Santiago Blas Molina

Software Developer

+54 11 49289536 santiagoblasmolina@gmail.com

Buenos Aires, Argentina

Work experience

PL/SQL Software Developer

Qaracter - Beyond your Challenge

Jul 2021 - Present

Madrid, Spain

Development and implementation of projects in the Back Office area of Santander Global Tech, using the PL/SQL language as a tool to satisfy user demands:

- Management of technology projects for the client Banco Santander
- Analysis and development of functional/technical requirements related to regulatory projects for Santander Global Tech.
- Developments in PL/SQL with SQL Developer.
- · Unix Bash Scripting
- Online/Batch Processing
- Participation in UATs connecting directly with the user.
- Production support in the post-implementation phases.
- · Deployment management.

FullStack Developer

Huapi Solutions

Mar 2022 - Present

Buenos Aires, Argentina

Design and development of web aplications projects working on both sides of each project (Frontend and Backend):

- Creation of responsive user interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Developed dynamic components using React for a better user experience.
- Built robust back-end servers using Node.js, managing client requests.
- Design and management of databases, such as MongoDB and MySQL.
- Collaboration in cross-functional teams to translate designs into functional code.

Education

Industrial Engineering

Universidad Nacional de La Plata

Mar 2016 - Mar 2021

Buenos Aires, Argentina

FullStack Developer

CoderHouse

Personal details

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/santiag

Website https://portafolio-sbmolina.com.ar/

Short bio

Graduated in Industrial Engineering. With specialization in the area of software development on both Frontend and Backend side, with preference for the server side. Passionate about code.

Languages

Spanish	Native speaker
English	Proficient

German Conversational

Skills

Mongo DB / My SQL

PL/SQL	Expert
HTML / CSS / SASS	Experienced
JavaScript	Experienced
Node.JS	Skillful
React JS	Skillful

Skillful

Jan 2021 - Dec 2023 Buenos Aires, Argentina